# **VUONG BUI**

#### SENIOR PHP DEVELOPER



#### **EXPERIENCES**

Apr 2016 - Present

STUDIO 60

#### PHP/Full-stack Developer

Team/Key member or full-stack developer. Work directly with a team in AU or client. Maintainance project that was pushed LIVE. Testing, fixing bug and support team. Report status to team leader and PM.

Nov 2015 - Apr 2016

**EKINO** 

#### PHP/Full-stack Developer

PHP/Full-stack developer. Converting design to HTML template and implement functions. Support tester, PM, report status to PM and manager of the root company.

May 2014 - Nov 2015

SUTRIX GROUP

#### Senior PHP Developer

Team/Key member or Full-stack developer. Working directly with teams in FR or client. Training and help the junior developer and team member.

Self-training and learn from other developers.

SKILL

PHP & MySQL

HTML & CSS

Javascript (Jquery)

Wordpress CMS

Laravel Framework

Symfony 2 Framework

GIT & SVN

Bootstrap

Windows/Linux

Codeigniter Framework

AJAX Jquery

RESTful API

**EDUCATION** 

Apr 2013 - May 2014

#### UNIWEB

#### PHP Junior Developer

PHP/Full-stack developer. Convert PSD to HTML and implement functions.

Testing, fix bug and report status to manager. Learn from the senior developer and self-training.

#### ABOUT ME

Hallo, my name is Vuong, I'm 25 years old and I'm a senior developer (a little confidence). I love coding, I love to build things, creative/crazy things. I'm strong at independent working but I love teamwork, why? A great man like Steve Jobs will be nothing if he works alone.

Jul 2010 - Jul 2013

# INDUSTRIAL UNIVERSITY OF HO CHI MINH CITY

Computer Science - Bachelors

#### CONTACT ME

- **Sep 09, 1992**
- 453 Le Van Khuong, Ho Chi Minh
- **J** 01664338026
- master@yopmail.com
- http://comingsoon.co
- f facebook.com/vuongabc92
- ♥ twitter.com/vuongabc92
- ☐ instagram.com/vuongabc92
- t tumblr.com/vuong
- linkedin.com/vuongabc92

# VUONG BUI

#### SENIOR PHP DEVELOPER



#### **EXPERIENCES**

Apr 2016 - Present

STUDIO 60

#### PHP/Full-stack Developer

Team/Key member or full-stack developer. Work directly with a team in AU or client. Maintainance project that was pushed LIVE. Testing, fixing bug and support team. Report status to team leader and PM.

Nov 2015 - Apr 2016

**EKINO** 

#### PHP/Full-stack Developer

PHP/Full-stack developer. Converting design to HTML template and implement functions. Support tester, PM, report status to PM and manager of the root company.

May 2014 - Nov 2015

SUTRIX GROUP

#### Senior PHP Developer

Team/Key member or Full-stack developer. Working directly with teams in FR or client. Training and help the junior developer and team member.

## SKILL

PHP & MySQL

HTML & CSS

Javascript (Jquery)

Wordpress CMS

Laravel Framework

Symfony 2 Framework

GIT & SVN

Bootstrap

Windows/Linux

Codeigniter Framework

AJAX Jquery

RESTful API

Self-training and learn from other developers.

Apr 2013 - May 2014

#### UNIWEB

#### PHP Junior Developer

PHP/Full-stack developer. Convert PSD to HTML and implement functions.

Testing, fix bug and report status to manager. Learn from the senior developer and self-training.

## ABOUT ME

Hallo, my name is Vuong, I'm 25 years old and I'm a senior developer (a little confidence). I love coding, I love to build things, creative/crazy things. I'm strong at independent working but I love teamwork, why? A great man like Steve Jobs will be nothing if he works alone.

#### **EDUCATION**

Jul 2010 - Jul 2013

INDUSTRIAL UNIVERSITY OF HO CHI MINH CITY

Computer Science - Bachelors

#### CONTACT ME

- **⊞** Sep 09, 1992
- 453 Le Van Khuong, Ho Chi Minh
- **J** 01664338026
- master@yopmail.com
- http://comingsoon.co
- **f** facebook.com/vuongabc92
- ♥ twitter.com/vuongabc92
- ☐ instagram.com/vuongabc92
- t tumblr.com/vuong
- in linkedin.com/vuongabc92